bloggerwave.com 2009-03-08

# Bloggerwave.com - Privacy Policy!

The following are the details of our Privacy Policy at Bloggerwave. We value the importance of privacy and consequently take care of all information received in a responsible manner. This Policy concerns all of the services offered by Bloggerwave. 

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and explains data collection and use practices for the IQ Division Network (IQD Network). The IQD Network includes all web pages, newsletters, discussion forums and lists including opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by IQ Division and each of its wholly owned subsidiaries including, without limitation, bloggerwave.com, iqdivision.com, reviewwave.com and exchangewave.com. By accessing the IQD Network you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**How do you collect stats?**  
IQD Network, its third party service providers and advertisers may use single-pixel GIF images sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons to count web page accesses and gather other general statistical information. IQD Network does not gather personal information through the use of these images. IQD Network does not use single-pixel GIFs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer. IQD Network may use third party providers to track and analyze non personally identifiable aggregate usage information from visitors to its websites in order to continuously improve the quality of its sites and services. 

**What personal information do you collect?**  
Whenever IQD Network collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name and e-mail address. 

IQD Network offers access to some services that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of these products and services. 

If you are purchasing something on the IQD Network we and any third party provider need to know your name, e-mail address and mailing address. This allows us or third party providers to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information will not be sold to third parties for any purpose except as provided in this Privacy Policy without your express permission. 

We will from time to time send e-mails announcing new products, opportunities and services. 

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**  
IQD Network will disclose personal information as follows: 

1\. To contact you regarding other products and services which may be of interest to you (including those we may offer jointly with other companies).  
2\. When required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:  
a) Co-operate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal processes served on IQD Network  
b) Protect and defend the rights or property of the IQD Network and related properties or visitors to the IQD Network and related properties  
c) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties or otherwise misusing the IQD Network or its related properties  
d) Fulfill a user's order or request  
3\. To process and fulfill your order or notify you of your order status  
4\. When we have your consent to share the information  
5\. When you use services within our network of sites you grant us permission to pass your registration information back to that service  

We maintain a strict "No Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

**Your consent to this agreement**  
By using the IQD Network you consent to the collection and use of information by IQD Network as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the type of information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
